I want to tell you today's VIP stock
[music]
Ravi Singh from Share India is with us to tell you the VIP stock. Very good
afternoon Ravi, which stock is on your radar
that will prove to be a VIP for the viewers?
Good afternoon, it is with
good momentum. The fundamental
numbers are supporting here and
if we look at it on an immediate basis, then there is a
target of 340 and if we keep a little longer then there was a
target of 380. These two levels are good and hence we
can enter the stock. It is
good here, so I think you can
include it in the VIP stock and
you can add good returns to your portfolio.
Okay, so yesterday we
saw very good momentum in metal stocks, but Vedanta is still
positive today. Selective profit taking is happening.
Targets of 340 are to be followed in Vedanta. The
price of 300 is around Rs 18. This VIP
stock is from Ravi. Thank you Ravi for
telling us this VIP stock.  To
suggest to our viewers and
how you can earn profit through options, we
will tell you its strategy and now the time has come for
profitable options
[music]
and today Amit Bhutani is present with us as Nirmal to find opportunities for earning from options and to
guide you.
Good
afternoon, it was
not the case, it can
go up to the level of 1450.
Thank you friends. I would say that you should
buy the call option of Chehra Show, the current price is
currently around ₹30. On the downside, the
stock will be plus on 16th. Now for the target of 50 to ₹60,
I feel that
ICICI General Insurance can
give a good profit from here. If Amit also has a call regarding space from China within four days, then you have to
buy the call of 1300 for ICICI Lombard. You have to buy the call of January series at the price of 30.
In this, the target will be ₹50 stock plus
₹16. So these strategies are for you
from our experts of options,
thank you very much for your time and this is
excellent.  Strategy to communicate to our audience